bug.co.uk 2003-12-20

# BUG Privacy Policy

|  | 

The following websites, operated by BUG Backpackers Guide, are covered by this privacy policy:
[backpackersultimateguide.com](http://www.backpackersultimateguide.com/), [bug.bz](http://www.bug.bz/), [bug.nu](http://www.bug.nu/), [australia.bugride.com](http://australia.bugride.com/), [europe.bugride.com](http://europe.bugride.com/), [pacific.bugride.com](http://pacific.bugride.com/), [bugride.com](http://www.bugride.com/), [bugaustralia.com](http://www.bugaustralia.com/), [bugeurope.com](http://www.bugeurope.com/), [bugpacific.com](http://www.bugpacific.com/) and [bugforums.com](http://www.bugforums.com/cgi-bin/ubbcgi/Ultimate.cgi).  

Our postal address is:  
2 Foam Street, Kilcunda, VIC 3995, Australia
We can be reached via e-mail at [tuden@bugeurope.com](mailto:tuden@bugeurope.com)  
or you can reach us by telephone at (03) 5678 7133, or +61 3 5678 7133 if you're calling from outside Australia.

BUG Backpackers Guide, and its advertisers and affiliates are absolutely committed to protecting your privacy. Below is information outlining our privacy policy and the responsible management of your information.

BUG does not proactively collect any personally identifiable information about you. However, the BUG websites do obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). This information collected by us is only aggregate statistical information used for the purpose of improving your experience and for targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers and affiliates.

BUG Backpackers Guide does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site.

### **Use of Cookies**

We use cookies on this site to remember your username and password and also to help you fill in hostel reviews and to prevent people from submitting multiple reviews about a single hostel. These cookies will only include information that you have entered while visiting one of the BUG websites. A cookie file may also be placed on your hard drive by third-party advertising companies or by affiliated companies which provide travel services through links from our websites.
A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. BUG Backpackers Guide uses non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to forms. You can still use the BUG sites if your browser is set to reject cookies. Our cookies do not generate personal data, do not read personal data from your machine and are never tied to anything that could be used to identify you. Since cookies cannot contain any program codes, they cannot be used to carry viruses.

### How we collect and use information  

### **BUG  Forums**

You are required to register to post messages on the BUG Forums discussion boards. When you register you are required to enter a username and your email address. All users have access to your username as well as the date you registered and your total number of posts. We do not ask for your real name and it is up to you whether you allow people to view your email address.

### **Hostel  Reviews**

If you wish you may post hostel reviews with your own name and email address which will be visible to all other people reading hostel reviews. However we do not force you to reveal your identity and you may post anonymous reviews if you wish to.

### **T-shirt Promotion**

BUG is running a promotion where we send a free t-shirt to users who post 20 messages to the forums or 20 hostel reviews. We will collect an address which is used to post the   
t-shirt. We do not keep this address and will not use the address for any other purpose.

### **Hostel Bookings**

Hostel bookings on BUG websites are processed by HostelWorld. Refer to [HostelWorld's privacy policy](http://217.114.161.100/privacy.php) for more information.

### **Affiliates**

We have partnered with travel companies to provide travel services promoted through the BUG websites. When you click on these links you are taken to our partners' website and are subject to their privacy policy.
For further information, consult the privacy policies of:  
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.

|
